so i was inspired by the good sis nicole bahari to really just take the time to extend a thank you
to y'all because the last like two years crazy right i mean for me personally like just you
know really standing like in just like basic like humanitarianism around like genocide around
halstein like around cuba around sudan and the congo like people just really can't like ride that
wave with you you know but it was really incredible to see how many of you did how many of you have right
like like so many of you have said amanda we're here we understand what you're about and we're
going to ride with you because we're about it too and that is the greatest surprise because i didn't
go this path thinking okay well everybody's gonna rock with me you know because i i just know this
is the path i have to go but when i see how many of you are just jumping the waves like me in grand
i say well oh god this is bigger than you this is bigger than you and if i'm keeping it up
but like there's just so many of y'all they have surprised me for just being like real people
you know like real like okay we solid like we not even playing with y'all like we not even
trying to pretend what is really going on because we see it it's a side we see it and yo to keep it
100 like i'm learning at the same time i'm teaching at the same time i'm learning at the same time you
teach you i mean like it's like a whole intercommunal situation you feel me like where we all just
done with the cap and we done with all that we just like yo we here we about this and i have to say that
that is what it's about it's about we must all come together we must all see each other for
uh what we are doing what we are about what we are for and understands that we have been lied to
so we must start telling the truth well because i don't know that i could do it for all of the time
i'm doing it if i was not supported by so many of you who are saying no amanda don't step back
step forward we are here with you we are here so i'd just like to thank you for all that you are
doing and all that you are saying and all that you are behaving and all that you are giving i appreciate
you come get these laughs and these high vibrations another radical rhythms experience goes down wednesday
august 12th at comedy and harley tickets link in bio